So, I have a model here.
And, what I want to show you all is that she has a base color that was applied.
And, it's a little bit darker.
And, she also has a highlight in there.
And, you can get a lot of different placements to blend gray.
This placement is a little bit more of a medium chunkier placement.
So, there's areas between the highlight versus the low light.
But, what happens with the gray is gray grows out.
It's normally just on the root or the base of the hair.
So, what tends to happen when you get the based covered the base actually covered with color.
And, then you go back in like our model has with a highlight lowlight it really is a good blending situation for the gray.
And, it's really color is all what you can compare it to what it lays against.
And, because you have a mixture and a dimensional look you're not focusing on the gray.
You're focusing on the other colors.
And, not as wide.
You should blend your gray with highlights and lowlights and a base color.